http://www.schoolsoftwares.com/privacy.html

Privacy Policy
As a general rule, this website does not collect Personal Information about you when you visit the site. You can generally visit the site without revealing Personal Information, unless you choose certain service provided to you like purchase or downloads of our products.
Visits Traffic:
This website records your visit and logs the following information for statistical purposes your IP address; type of browser you use; the date and time you access the site; the pages you have accessed and the documents downloaded and the previous Internet address from which you linked directly to the site.
We will not identify users or their browsing activities, except when a law enforcement agency may exercise a warrant to inspect the service provider’s logs.
Cookies:
A cookie is a piece of software code that an internet web site sends to your browser when you access information at that site. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Schoolsoftwares.com uses cookies to track user traffic and for the personalization feature.
Electronic Newsletters:
Your email address will only be recorded if you choose to subscribe for updates of our website. It will only be used for the purpose for which you have provided it and will not be added to a mailing list. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by using the link provided in every newsletter. Your email address will not be used for any other purpose, and will not be disclosed, without your consent.
Collection of Personal Information:
If you are asked for any other Personal Information you will be informed how it will be used if you choose to give it. If at any time you believe the principles referred to in this privacy statement have not been followed, or have any other comments on these principles, please notify the webmaster through the contact us page.
Note: The use of the term “Personal Information” in this privacy statement refers to any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.
Contacting Us:
We welcome your suggestions or feedback to improve our service and request that any error found may kindly be brought to our notice or the practices of this site or your dealings with this website contact Genuine InfoTech Private Limited. Thanks for visiting our site.
Get Started
Take a demo; get a quote or just more information
Have us contact you :
or, Call Us
Phone : 91- 422 - 4371212
: 91- 422 - 2446043
For Product Enquiry (New Clients) :
093600 39678
094430 59678
For Software Support (Existing Clients) :
094890 69678
Fax No. : 0422-4371212
Time Table
Frame your school timetable in a short time without any clashes which results in 100% accuracy.
Question Paper
Get into the process of Question bank Creation with multilanguage support & generate the question paper in no time.
Fees Collection
Manage your school fees collection activities efficiently in your regional language & get away from human errors.
Student Management
Record & Preserve the details of students as per formal process from Admission to Relieving in a powerful & secured database.
Mark & Rank Card
Manage your school Rank card preparation process smoothly & print predefined comparison reports & charts instantly.
School Automation Software Products :
Remote Support (Teamviewer)
Time: 9.15 am to 6.00 pm [Mon-Sat]
Skype ID : helpschoolsoftware
Copyright © 2020 Schoolsoftwares.com, Genuine InFoTech Private Limited
,Coimbatore, Tamilnadu, India - All Rights Reserved.
Our Portals : www.winentrance.com , www.upscexam.com, www.emporiumonnet.com,
www.wisdom24x7.com
